(Howard:)Oh, come on, that can't be true.
(Raj:)I did the research. Tony the Tiger...
...Dig 'Em the frog, Cap'N Crunch, Toucan
Sam, Count Chocula, Trix the Rabbit...
(Raj:)...Snap, Crackle and Pop.
(Raj:)Not one cereal mascot is a girl.
(Raj:)It's a total breakfast sausage fest.
(Leonard:)Are we done with this?
(Raj:)Almost. Franken Berry, Boo Berry,
Sugar Bear, and the Honey Nut Cheerio Bee.
(Raj:)I believe his name is Buzz.
(Leonard:)Terrific. Something weird happened
and I don't know what to do about it.
- What's going on?
- Sheldon's assistant...
(Leonard:)...asked me on a date.
(Raj:)How could you do that to me?
(Raj:)You know I've been working it
with Alex for weeks.
(Leonard:)Working it? You can't even talk to her.
(Raj:)I talk with my eyes.
(Howard:)You look like my little cousin when
he's dropping one in his diaper.